# Maria Arouje

Mariaarouje@gmail.com +923092238181 LinkedIn Portfolio GitHub

## **OBJECTIVE**

I am a dedicated and motivated individual with a strong academic background in Computer Science & IT,

Complemented by practical experience in UI/UX, front end web development, teaching, management, and sales. With a passion for learning and a commitment to excellence.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Social Media Intern (3-07-2024 to 03-08-2024)

1 month

- Company: GS GLOBAL (Online selling company)
- Responsibilities: social media accounts creation and optimization, Follow back strategies on instagram for Orbitors, content strategies, content calendar, Voice Over ads.

## **Digital Marketing Manager** (01-08-2021 to 01-04-2022)

8 months

- Company: GS GLOBAL (Online selling company)
- Meta suit Ad management, Strategies for increasing sales.

# **Internship:** (01-04-2019 to 01-08-2020)

17 months

- Organization: Bacha Khan Trust Educational Foundation
- **Departments:** Management and Finance
- Responsibilities: Writing meeting minutes, social media management, library management, record-keeping, generating progress reports, etc.

## **Teaching:** (01-0-2016 to 01-08-2016)

2 months

- Institution: Iqra rozat ul AtFal School Shagai Peshawar
- Subjects: All subjects for 4th class

#### SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, C++, JAVA, Canva, Figma, MetriCool, Notion.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS: Project Management, Digital Marketing, Social Media, Customer Support, Communication, Time Management Approachable, Effective Group & Individual workability, Active Listener

#### **CERTIFICATION/TRAININGS:**

- Introduction to software Programming and Database
- Supervised Machine Learning Regression and Classification
- Speak English Professionally in person, online and on the phone call.
- Competitor in Zindagi Prize presenting ideas.
- International Mathematics Contest Training

## **Participation Certificate**:

- Political Leadership, Democracy and Active Leadership
- 3 Days Training & Conference on Confidence Building & Public speaking "CPS" Organized by Social Welfare & Awareness Society in May 2014.
- Certificate of completing 5-days teachers training course in "Bacha Khan Reading Skills Development Program" from May 1st to May 5th, 2018.
- Certificate for successfully completing a two-day workshop on human rights and advocacy for human right defenders.
- Participation at co-curricular activities
- Workshop for women empowerment

## EDUCATION:

Bachelor of Computer Science and information Technology UET, Peshawar, KPK (Cgpa 3.72)

FSc (pre engineering) Jinnah College For Women UOP, Peshawar, KPK (A)

Nov 2020 - July 2024 Aug 2016-June 2018

Hssc (Science) Warsak Model School Peshawar, KPK (A1)

Mar 2008-May 2016

#### LANGAGE

English, Urdu, Pushto.